<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Edwin Miguel, My Site</title>
    <link>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Edwin Miguel, My Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 14:03:55 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://emiguelt.mysu.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux on asus transformer T101H</title>
      <link>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/posts/2018/linux_on_asus_transformer_t100ha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 07:33:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/posts/2018/linux_on_asus_transformer_t100ha/</guid>
      <description>Problems found installing *ubuntu 18.04/18.10 on an Asus Transformer T101H
ERROR (Xubuntu 18.04): GDBus.Error.org.freedesktop.login1 SleepVerbNotSupported Solution:  edit /etc/modprobe.d/blacklist.conf and add the following line:
blacklist snd_hdmi_lpe_audio
 reboot
  ERROR (Lubuntu 18.04): Backlight not working  Check if /sys/class/backlight link file exists. If does not exist, create like in this tutorial: https://askubuntu.com/a/715310/578393. On Asus T101H: /sys/class/backlight/intel_backlight -&amp;gt; ../../devices/pci0000:00/0000:00:02.0/drm/card0/card0-DSI-1/intel_backlight
 Create the /etc/X11/xorg.conf file with:
   Section &amp;quot;Device&amp;quot; Identifier &amp;quot;Intel Graphics&amp;quot; Driver &amp;quot;intel&amp;quot; Option &amp;quot;Backlight&amp;quot; &amp;quot;intel_backlight&amp;quot; EndSection   The backlight will work with ctrl+f10 and ctrl+f11 (Pending, change to fn+f5 and fn+f6 keys)  Enable autorotation  Identify the display ID: Execute xrandr and check the name, for Asus T101H is DSI1 Identify the touchscren ID  Execute xinput Identify all slave pointer devices You can disable/enable de device and touch the display to test if is the correct device: xinput disable &amp;lt;ID&amp;gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips</title>
      <link>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/posts/2018/tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 15:03:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/posts/2018/tips/</guid>
      <description>This post contains some useful tips related with my daily work in software development like commands, database, ssh, etc. It is mainly as a reference for me, but it could be useful for other person.
PDF  Remove the password from many PDF files and join in single file (QPDF): Assuming all pdfs are in the folder and has the same password  for F in *; do qpdf --password=&amp;lt;THE_PASSWORD&amp;gt; --decrypt $F d_$F; rm $F; done; qpdf --empty &amp;lt;MERGED_NAME&amp;gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools</title>
      <link>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/posts/2018/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 17:50:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/posts/2018/tools/</guid>
      <description> This entry coverages some tools I found useful during my work in software development (Windows and Linux), most of the open source
   Tool Description OS Free     Babun windows shell based on Cygwin. I use it with tmux :) W y   DBeaver as its site says, a Universal Database tool WL y   ConEmu excellent terminal emulator for Windows, something like &amp;ldquo;tmux&amp;rdquo; (not as sophisticated), and compatible with many terminals (cmd, powershell, git-bash :), etc) W y   KeePass tool to manage your passwords in secure way WL y   Q-Dir file explorer with support to splits and tabs W y   WinDirStat Tool to analyze hard disk to remove big files, there is KDirStat for Linux WL y   Conda dependency &amp;amp; environment management for many languages WL y   Grip render markdown files locally WL y   trang java project to generate xsd from xml samples WL y   Process Explorer Check processes in Windows and which one has opened an specific file W y    Conventions  OS (Operating System):  Linux: L, Windows: W   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/posts/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/posts/contact/</guid>
      <description>Loading... </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books I read in 2018</title>
      <link>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/posts/2018/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://emiguelt.mysu.co/posts/2018/books/</guid>
      <description>Deep Work - Cal Newport Excellent book for people looking how to improve their focus on knowledge tasks and get things done.
The book is divided in two main parts, in the first one, the author justifies why it is important to be focus and having a well structured strategy to reach our objective. The second part presents a set of 4 rules to follow in order to improve our performance in the activities we are interested in.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>